I'm addicted 끊임없이 말을 걸어주는 나의 aespa aespa!
I’m addicted、絶え間なく話しかけてくれる私のaespa
I’m addicted endlessly talking to me, my aespa
이런 교감 너의 존잰 날 다른 차원으로 이끌었지
この共感、君の存在は私を別次元に導いてくれた
This communion, your existence brings me to another dimension
난 세상 중심에 You're in the FLAT FLAT!
私は世界の中心に、You’re in the FLAT
I’m at the center of the world, you’re in the FLAT
내 모든 action 어린 너의 힘을 키워
私の全てのAction 幼い君に力を与える
All of my Action, it grows your power
넌 언젠가부터 synk out 노이즈같이 보여
君はいつからかSYNK out 、ノイズのように見える
From some time ago you SYNK out, looking like a noise
더 이상 못 찾겠어
もう見つけられない
I can’t find it anymore
널 유혹해 삼킨 건 Black Mamba
君を誘惑し飲み込んだのはBlack Mamba
The temptation that swallows you, Black Mamba
Ma Ma Ma Mamba aespa!
Woo oh-oh
Oh eh-o eh-o
넌 광야를 떠돌고 있어
君はKWANGYAを彷徨っている
You wander this KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
나의 분신을 찾고 싶어
私の分身を見つけたい
I wanna find your other self
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba
I hate Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Hate Ma Ma Ma Mamba
I'm ejected 선함 만으론 (Woo) 너의 거대함을 이기지 못해 못해!
I’m ejected, 善意だけでは巨大な君に勝てない
I’m ejected, good is not enough to break your greatness
I'm exhausted 너의 존잰 모든 탐욕들을 먹고 자라 났지
I’m exhausted, 君の存在は全ての貪欲を飲み込んで成長した
I’m exhausted, your existence has grown swallowing all of the greed
​aespa는 나야 둘이 될 수 없어 없어!
aespaは私、二つにはなれない
I’m the aespa, there can’t be two
Monochrome to colors
이건 evo-evolution
これはEvo, Evolution
This is Evo, Evolution
Oh, 위험한 장난을 쳐 매혹적이지만 널 부정할 밖에
Oh!危険ないたずら。魅惑的だけど君を否定せざるを得ない
Oh! I make a dangerous joke, you’re charming but gotta deny
모든 걸 삼켜버릴 Black Mamba
全てを飲み込みそうなBlack Mamba
It will swallow everything, Black Mamba
Ma Ma Ma Mamba aespa!
Woo oh-oh
Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Oh eh-o eh-o
넌 광야를 떠돌고 있어
君はKWANGYAを彷徨っている
You wander this KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
네게 맞서 난 질 수 없어
君に対抗して、私は負けられない
I can't lose against you
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba
거울 속의 나는 네가 아닐까?
鏡の中の私は君ではない？
Is me in the mirror you
일그러져버린 환영인 걸까?
歪んでしまった幻影なのだろうか
Is it just a distorted vision
다시 너와 연결될 수 있다면
また君と繋がれるのならば
If I could connect with you again
너를 만나고 싶어 (Hey) 이제
もうすでに君に会いたい
I want to meet you now
모든 걸 삼켜버릴 Black Mamba
全てを飲み込みそうなBlack Mamba
It will swallow everything, Black Mamba
>Ma Ma Ma Mamba aespa!
>Woo oh-oh
>Oh eh-o eh-o
>넌 광야를 떠돌고 있어
君はこの KWANGYAを彷徨っている
You wander this KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
네게 맞서 난 질 수 없어
君に対抗して、私は負けられない
I can't lose against you
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba